So in an effort to diversify those that are demonstrating being high quality, I do the
high quality white series. I don't think y'all understand how many times I will post
a white person as a high quality white and have to then take it down because people then
tell me, actually, this white has a number of low quality opinions, actions, etc. outside
of this one. Because, you know, I'm thinking like, well, if you stand on this, then this
is representation of your whole character. No, no. I just had to take down a high quality
white for a fighter named Bryce Mitchell.
Did you see that Sean Strickland got banned from the White House for talking about Israel?
I'm not surprised at all. I mean, it, you know, freedom of speech is what really makes
this country great. And when you can't criticize a foreign nation, a foreign nation, come on,
man, we ought to be able to criticize our own nation, let alone a foreign nation. In fact,
that's the only nation you're not allowed to criticize. You know, so something's going
to change because evil empires don't last forever. There's always a rebellion. You ever
seen Star Wars? That's what's going to happen, bro. Darth Vader's going to get took down.
Saying what needed to be said about Israel because they were like, yeah, actually, he's
like a full racist. I guess a broken racist is right twice a day. Why does y'all need to
get it right?
I'm back in my music bag and Amanda Diva 2.0 is loading. My new album, Truth Translator,
drops June 14th. Head to AmandaDivaMusic.com to hear the album, to support the work through
merch, and to find out when I'm going to be in your city with a free sound session.
This ain't a movement, it's movement music.
I am so...